{
    "questions" : 
    [
        {
            "question": "Write method with one argument, which you need to use to get the 2D drawing context for drawing 2D graphics on canvas",
            "correctAnswer": "getContext('2d')",
            "typeQuestion": "text"
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you call a function named 'myFunction'?",
            "correctAnswer": "myFunction()",
            "typeQuestion": "text"
        },
        {   
        "question": "Which code block would allow for a color change of the outline shape or line to green.",
        "answers": {
            "a": "ctx.fillStyle = 'green';",
            "b": "ctx.strokeStyle = 'green';",
            "c": "ctx.lineStyle = 'green';",
            "d": "ctx.fillLine = 'green';"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which code block allows the programmer to draw various shapes and lines on to the canvas?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "var ctx = document.getElementById('myCanvas').getContext('2d');",
                "b": "var c = document.getElementById('myCanvas');",
                "c": "draw();",
                "d": "function canvasDraw();"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "a",
            "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Canvas?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "Canvas is a CSS property, with which you can choose the shape type.",
                "b": "Canvas is a HTML Tag which is used to include an image within a webpage or website",
                "c": "Canvas is an XML-based vector image format for defining two-dimensional graphics, having support for interactivity and animation",
                "d": "Canvas in a HTML 5 element that is used to draw graphics and different types of shapes by using JavaScript."
            },
            "correctAnswer": "d",
            "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you round the number 9.25, to the nearest integer?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "Math.rnd(9.25)",
                "b": "round(9.25)",
                "c": "rnd(9.25)",
                "d": "Math.round(9.25)"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "d",
            "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question": "How to correctly display a greeting after 5 seconds?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "sleep(5); alert('Hello!'); ",
                "b": "sleep(5000); alert('Hello!');",
                "c": "setTimeout(function() {alert('Hello!')}, 5000);",
                "d": "setTimeout(function() {alert('Hello!')}, 5);"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "c",
            "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "onmouseover",
                "b": "onclick",
                "c": "onchange",
                "d": "onmouseclick"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "b",
            "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is it possible to get the content of a comment from JavaScript?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "Yes, the comment is a DOM node, you can get it",
                "b": "No, comments are in the HTML but not in the DOM",
                "c": "You can get it, but only until the page is loaded",
                "d": "Yes, you can do it with getComment() method"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "a",
            "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which event from this list does NOT exist?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "onwheel",
                "b": "onclick",
                "c": "onmousescroll",
                "d": "onmousemove"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "c",
            "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question": "How to apply strict mode in JavaScript?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "“strict mode”",
                "b": "“use strict”",
                "c": "“apply strict”",
                "d": "“strict”"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "b",
            "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question": "Java Script entities start with _____ and end with _____.",
            "answers": {
                "a": "dash, semicolon",
                "b": "ampersand, colon",
                "c": "semicolon, dash",
                "d": "ampersand, semicolon"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "d",
            "typeQuestion" : "radio"
        },
        {
            "question" : "How to work with rectangles inside canvas?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "fillRect",
                "b": "lineRect",
                "c": "moveRect",
                "d": "strokeRect",
                "e": "clearRect"
            } ,
            "correctAnswer": ["a", "d", "e"],
            "typeQuestion" : "checkbox"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Where is the correct place to insert a JavaScript?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "The body section",
                "b": "The head section",
                "c": "The header section"
            },
            "correctAnswer": ["a", "b"],
            "typeQuestion" : "checkbox"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which events from this list will occur when you press and release the Shift key? Other keys are not pressed.",
            "answers": {
                "a": "keydown",
                "b": "keyup",
                "c": "keypress",
                "d": "keyrelease"
            },
            "correctAnswer": ["a", "c"],
            "typeQuestion" : "checkbox"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of these element properties can point to a text node?",
            "answers": {
                "a": "firstChild",
                "b": "nextSibling",
                "c": "parentNode",
                "d": "parentElement"
            },
            "correctAnswer": ["a", "c", "d"],
            "typeQuestion" : "checkbox"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the difference between fillRect and strokeRect?",
            "tasks":[
                {
                    "sentence": "fillRect let us draw a rectangle which is ",
                    "answers": [
                        "filled",
                        "empty but with only outline"
                    ],
                    "correctAnswer": "filled"
                },
                {
                    "sentence": "strokeRect let us draw a rectangle ",
                    "answers": [
                        "that is completely filled",
                        "with only outline"      
                    ],
                    "correctAnswer": "with only outline"
                }
            ],

            "typeQuestion" : "list"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the difference between confirm and prompt dialog box?",
            "tasks":[
                {
                    "sentence": "confirm(): Display a popup box with ",
                    "answers": [
                        "a question and two buttons: OK and Cancel",
                        "the specified message and waits for the user to press OK. ",
                        "a text message, an input field for the visitor, and the buttons OK/Cancel" 
                    ],
                    "correctAnswer": "a question and two buttons: OK and Cancel"
                },
                {
                    "sentence": "prompt(): Display a popup box with ",
                    "answers": [
                        "a question and two buttons: OK and Cancel",
                        "the specified message and waits for the user to press 'OK'. ",
                        "a text message, an input field for the visitor, and the buttons OK/Cancel" 
                    ],
                    "correctAnswer": "a text message, an input field for the visitor, and the buttons OK/Cancel"
                }
            ],

            "typeQuestion" : "list"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Match definition and meaning",
            "definitions" : [
                "undefined", "null", "Object"
            ],
            "answers": [
                "Represents the intentional absence of any object value",
                "A data type whose variable is not initialized",
                "Data type which contain key-value pairs of collection of data"
            ],
            "correctAnswers": {
                "undefined": "A data type whose variable is not initialized",
                "null": "Represents the intentional absence of any object value",
                "Object": "Data type which contain key-value pairs of collection of data"
            },
            "typeQuestion" : "match"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Match definition and meaning",
            "definitions" : [
                "Symbol", "String", "Boolean"
            ],
            "answers": [
                "Data type whose instances are unique and immutable",
                "Primitive data types that have one of two possible values. This values are usually used for conditional operations",
                "Data type which represents textual data"
            ],
            "correctAnswers": {
                "Symbol": "Data type whose instances are unique and immutable",
                "String": "Data type which represents textual data",
                "Boolean": "Primitive data types that have one of two possible values. This values are usually used for conditional operations"
            },
            "typeQuestion" : "match"
        }
    ]
}
